>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们深入讨论这个平等话题，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's dig in
a bit on this topic of equality,
因为有很多肉是我们在平等的条件下进行的
because there's a lot of meat that we
just went over in terms of equality.
所以我们要有一个专门的练习
So we wanna have a whole
exercise dedicated to this.
公平的警告，这项工作将会受到公平的处理。
And fair warning, this exercise
is going to be fairly involved.
有很多细微的细微差别我们都要处理
There's a lot of little nuances that
we're gonna have to take care of.
我要你做的事
What I am asking you to
do with this exercise
你要写一个 findAll 实用程序
is you're going to write
a findAll utility.
此 findAll 实用程序通过数组进行搜索，查找范围内的任何值
And this findAll utility searches through
an array, looking for any values within
与您传入的某些测试值相等的阵列。
the array that are coercively equal to
some test value that you've passed in.
但在这一强制性平等问题上存在一些非常具体的制约因素。
But there are some very specific
constraints on that coercive equality.
所以，当然，这并不像只应用双等号那么简单。
So it's, of course, not as simple
as just applying a double equals.
因此 findAll 实用程序需要返回具有所有匹配值的数组
So the findAll utility needs to return
an array with all of the values that match
指示信息中描述的测试规则。
the test rules as described
here in the instructions.
所以我们想要的强迫性匹配，不仅是双等号，
So the coercive matching that we want,
which is not just the double equals,
是完全匹配的，我们现在知道可以用这个对象点。
is any exact matches, which we now know
we can use an object dot this for.
任何确实的比赛，我们当然都想加入。
And any exact matches, we,
of course, want to include.
如果有任何字符串，除了空字符串或
If there are any strings,
except for the empty string or
只会有白色的地方记得我们想忽略那些
white space only, remember,
we wanna ignore those, but
如果有任何字符串，他们就可以被强迫匹配号码。
if there are any strings, they're
allowed to coercively match numbers.
如果有数字除了 NaN 和无穷大之外
And if there are any numbers,
other than NaN and the infinities,
允许这些字符匹配字符串。
those are allowed to match strings.
但就像一点点提示要小心和 0
But as a little bit of a hint,
be very careful with -0,
因为它会把扳手扔进几个测试用的好吗
because it will throw a wrench into
several of these test cases, okay?
我们想让空值与未定义的匹配项匹配，并且
We wanna allow null to match undefined,
and
反之亦然这就直说了
vise versa,
that's pretty straight forward.
我们想让博文人只与其他的野人相匹配
We wanna allow booleans only
to match other booleans.
因此， true 仅匹配 true，而不是字符串 true 或数字匹配。
So true only matches true,
not the string true, or the number one,
或者任何类似的事情
or anything like that.
任何不是原始的东西就像任何物体一样
And anything that's not a primitive,
like any of the objects,
这些都是严格的身份匹配
those are strictly identity only matching.
因此，不需要实施任何结构检查。
So no structural checking
that you need to implement.
在我们的 ex.js 文件中，您会注意到我们在这里有一堆测试用例。
In our ex.js file, you'll notice that
we have a bunch of test cases here.
底部有一个功能只会用于
And there's a function at the bottom
which is only being used for
测试用例的用途。
the purposes of the test case.
它正在检查以确保这些数组包含相同的值，并且
It's checking to make sure that these
arrays contain the same values, and
就算他们有不同的命令
then even if they're in different orders.
这些都是我们正在检查的测试用例。
So these are all of our test
cases that we're checking for.
你能通过那些测试用例
It would be useful for
you to go through those test cases to make
请确保您了解自述文件的内容。
sure you understand what
the readme is saying.
但您想做的是实现一个 findAll ，它可以采用此值数组，并且
But you wanna do is implement a findAll
which can take this values array and
比如说，让我们来这里就一个吧。
a value like, for example,
let's just take one here.
因此 findAll 采用 -0 和值，并且
So the findAll takes the -0 and
the values, and
它应该只返回一个数组，其中包含一个 -0 。
it should only return an array
with a single -0 in it.
但是，例如，如果将 findAll with "0" 传递，
But for example,
if you pass findAll with "0",
那么应该同时找到常规 0 和引号 0，好吗 ?
then that should find both
the regular 0 and the quote 0, okay?
但愿那是合理的
Hopefully that makes sense.
因此，我们要花一点时间，因为这牵涉到更多的问题。
So we will take a bit more time
because this is more involved.
你会写几个不同的条款
You're gonna write several
different clauses and
来处理这些问题的
if statements to handle all of these.
如果你错过了这些案子也别难过了
And don't feel bad if you
miss some of these cases,
我们这里有很多细微的差别
cuz there's a lot of nuance here.
运动的重点是让你思考
The point of the exercise is
to get you thinking about,
如何限制这种情况，使我有一套安全的强制比较?
how do I restrict this so that I have
a safe set of coercive comparisons?